<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Ben the Pen - Winners &amp; Whiners - Sportsbooks</title>
	<atom:link href="https://winnersandwhiners.com/author/ben-the-pen/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://winnersandwhiners.com/betting</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 16:36:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://wp.winnersandwhiners.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/favicon.png</url>
	<title>Ben the Pen - Winners &amp; Whiners - Sportsbooks</title>
	<link>https://winnersandwhiners.com/betting</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>How To Bet the Preakness: 5 Key Questions Answered</title>
		<link>https://winnersandwhiners.com/betting/horse-racing/how-to-bet-the-preakness-5-key-questions-answered-431/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ben the Pen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 21:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[How to Bet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US Horse Racing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pimlico Race Course]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Preakness Stakes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wp.winnersandwhiners.com/?p=431</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking to make a big score in the second jewel of the Triple Crown? The 148th Preakness Stakes goes on Saturday, May 20 from the famed Pimlico Race Course in Baltimore. If you have questions regarding this race, we have the answers. </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://winnersandwhiners.com/betting/horse-racing/how-to-bet-the-preakness-5-key-questions-answered-431/">How To Bet the Preakness: 5 Key Questions Answered</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://winnersandwhiners.com/betting">Winners &amp; Whiners - Sportsbooks</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The Preakness Stakes, as the second jewel in horse racing&#8217;s illustrious Triple Crown, offers a unique blend of challenges and opportunities for both seasoned bettors and casual fans. A thorough understanding of its history, trends, and peculiarities can provide a critical edge in making successful wagers. To assist you, we&#8217;ve addressed five key questions that could shape your betting strategy for this year&#8217;s race. From examining past winners&#8217; paths to debunking popular myths about the course, we&#8217;re here to guide you through the intricacies of betting the Preakness. Let&#8217;s dive in.</p>



<h3 id='1-how-do-kentucky-derby-winners-do-in-the-preakness'  id="boomdevs_1" class="wp-block-heading" >#1: How do Kentucky Derby winners do in the Preakness?</h3>



<p>In the new millennium, 8 Derby winners have clinched the Preakness title. Notably, this includes the trio of War Emblem, Funny Cide, and Smarty Jones, who all triumphed consecutively from 2002-2004. Despite this, the recent trend seems to favor the fresh contenders, colloquially known as &#8220;new shooters&#8221;. The last two Derby winners to win the Preakness went on to complete the prestigious Triple Crown.</p>



<p>This year, Mage will attempt to complete the Kentucky Derby/Preakness double with hopes of competing for the Triple Crown.</p>



<p><a href="https://wp.winnersandwhiners.com/horse-racing/2023-preakness-picks-with-exacta-trifecta-and-superfecta-predictions-420/" data-type="post" data-id="420">See our 2023 Preakness picks: exactas, trifecta, and superfecta from the Expert who won the Kentucky Derby Exacta!</a></p>



<h3 id='2-how-many-preakness-winners-did-not-run-in-the-kentucky-derby'  id="boomdevs_2" class="wp-block-heading" >#2: How many Preakness winners did not run in the Kentucky Derby?</h3>



<p>In a somewhat recent trend, non-Derby runners have started to dominate the Preakness. For example, in the last 6 years, 4 Preakness winners did not participate in the Kentucky Derby. This includes the champions of the past three years. However, this trend only began to surface around 2017, with Rachel Alexandra&#8217;s 2009 victory standing as an outlier.</p>



<p>This year, all but one contender, Kentucky Derby winner Mage, will be new shooters lookinng to claim thier spot in the Preakness winner circle.</p>



<h3 id='3-what-is-the-optimal-running-style-of-past-preakness-winners'  id="boomdevs_3" class="wp-block-heading" >#3: What is the optimal running style of past Preakness winners?</h3>



<p>Preakness victories aren&#8217;t typically claimed by runaway leaders. While there are a few exceptions like Justify in 2018, Oxbow in 2013, and Shackleford in 2011, a more strategic approach often seems to yield success. The &#8216;ideal&#8217; running style appears to involve staying near the front of the pack, ready to make a decisive move near the stretch. Big rallies from horses far behind have been a rarity in the Preakness.</p>



<p>This year&#8217;s likley horses that fit the ideal running style are 1 National Treasure (4-1) and 8 First Mission (5/2).</p>



<h3 id='4-fact-or-fiction-does-pimlico-really-have-8220-tight-turns-8221'  id="boomdevs_4" class="wp-block-heading" >#4: Fact or Fiction: Does Pimlico really have &#8220;Tight Turns?&#8221;</h3>



<p>A longstanding belief about Pimlico&#8217;s &#8220;tight turns&#8221; affecting the Preakness has been debunked. Extensive research by the Daily Racing Form revealed that Pimlico and Churchill Downs (where the Derby is held) have the exact same circumference. Pimlico is slightly narrower, resulting in less banking in the turns, but the difference is marginal and not significantly impactful.</p>



<h3 id='5-what-are-the-most-successful-post-positions-in-the-preakness'  id="boomdevs_5" class="wp-block-heading" >#5: What are the most successful post positions in the Preakness?</h3>



<p>The 6 position has proven to be the most successful among Preakness winners, boasting 17 victories, including the 2021 winner, Rombauer. This year, Perform at odds of 15-1 draws the 6 position in the Preakenss. Other notable positions are 4 and 7, each of which has recorded 13 wins.</p>



<p>The 4 this year is Coffeewithchris (20-1) and the 7 is Blazing Sevens (6-1).</p>



<h2 id='bonus-questions'  id="boomdevs_6" class="wp-block-heading" >Bonus questions!</h2>



<p>Keep reading to find out the average payouts for the Preakness.</p>



<h3 id='what-is-the-average-win-payout-in-the-preakness'  id="boomdevs_7" class="wp-block-heading" >What is the average win payout in the Preakness?</h3>



<p>Since 1990, placing a $2 win bet in the Preakness has yielded an average return of $10.90.</p>



<h3 id='what-is-the-average-exacta-payout-in-the-preakness'  id="boomdevs_8" class="wp-block-heading" >What is the average exacta payout in the Preakness?</h3>



<p>The average Exacta payout in the Preakness has also been lucrative. Since 1990, a $2 Exacta bet has returned an average of $99.87.</p>



<h3 id='what-is-the-average-trifecta-payout-in-the-preakness'  id="boomdevs_9" class="wp-block-heading" >What is the average trifecta payout in the Preakness?</h3>



<p>Since 1990, the average trifecta has been particularly rewarding, paying out a considerable $928.10</p>



<h3 id='for-the-first-time-in-triple-crown-history-8230'  id="boomdevs_10" class="wp-block-heading" >For the First time in Triple Crown History&#8230;</h3>



<p>For a dose of trivia, consider this: Since the establishment of the current Triple Crown schedule in 1969, this year marks the first instance where only a single horse from the Kentucky Derby, namely Mage, will be participating in the Preakness.</p>



<p>If you’re not betting the Preakness in-person and would like to bet from the comfort of your own, it’s easy to do. Just find a bonus offer from one of these racebooks and click the link to sign up.</p>



<p><strong>Option #1:</strong> <a href="https://www.amwager.com/?amwaffid=Winnersandwhiners.com" data-type="URL" data-id="https://www.amwager.com/?amwaffid=Winnersandwhiners.com" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener sponsored">Click here to sign up and AmWager will give you a 100% First Deposit Match Bonus, of up to $150.</a></p>



<p><strong>Option #2:</strong> <a href="https://www.twinspires.com/bet/offers/TWIN400/details?&amp;utm_source=Affiliate&amp;utm_medium=IncomeAccess&amp;utm_term=2870" target="_blank" data-type="URL" data-id="https://www.twinspires.com/bet/offers/TWIN400/details?&amp;utm_source=Affiliate&amp;utm_medium=IncomeAccess&amp;utm_term=2870" rel="noreferrer noopener sponsored">TwinSpires is offering a $400 sign-up Bonus for new online betting accounts!</a></p>



<p>*Please visit all the sites for the exact terms and conditions of their offers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://winnersandwhiners.com/betting/horse-racing/how-to-bet-the-preakness-5-key-questions-answered-431/">How To Bet the Preakness: 5 Key Questions Answered</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://winnersandwhiners.com/betting">Winners &amp; Whiners - Sportsbooks</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kentucky Derby Superfecta Betting Strategy to turn $10 into $20,000</title>
		<link>https://winnersandwhiners.com/betting/horse-racing/kentucky-derby-superfecta-betting-strategy-to-turn-10-into-20000-454/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ben the Pen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 23:39:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Horse Racing Predictions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US Horse Racing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Churchill Downs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kentucky Derby]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wp.winnersandwhiners.com/?p=454</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Easy step by step guide on how to bet my $10 budget superfecta strategy with projected payout of over $20,000!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://winnersandwhiners.com/betting/horse-racing/kentucky-derby-superfecta-betting-strategy-to-turn-10-into-20000-454/">Kentucky Derby Superfecta Betting Strategy to turn $10 into $20,000</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://winnersandwhiners.com/betting">Winners &amp; Whiners - Sportsbooks</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div class="alert alert-danger">

<div class="alert-text text-danger"><strong>IMPORTANT!</strong> This is an old article. Please <a href="https://wp.winnersandwhiners.com/horse-racing/get-set-to-freakin-crush-it-at-the-kentucky-derby-parlay-bettors-all-ears-443/">click here to read this year&#8217;s betting strategy on the Kentucky Derby!</a>
</div>
</div>



<p>Turning $10 into $20,000 sounds too good to be true, and you’d be right if I was talking about sports. I’m talking about Horse Racing, and specifically the Kentucky Derby this weekend.</p>



<p>Know nothing about horses? That’s fine, stick with me here and I’ll explain why.</p>



<p>First, I have a sign-up offer from our partners at Daily Racing Form which will give you $10 free for just signing up. No need to deposit anything! (Offer expired, <a href="https://winnersandwhiners.com/articles/get-set-to-freakin-crush-it-at-the-kentucky-derby-parlay-bettors-all-ears-predictions-below__ca+8157">click here</a> for this year&#8217;s best offers.)</p>



<p>Second, I am going to give you the exact wagers that have the best chance to turn that free $10 into $20k that you can take home.</p>



<p>Still skeptical? Let me explain what makes Horse Racing different from sports betting and why I love the ponies and you should too.</p>



<h3 id='why-you-should-bet-on-horse-racing'  id="boomdevs_1" class="wp-block-heading" ><strong>Why you should bet on Horse Racing</strong></h3>



<p>In horse racing, all wagers are done in a pool. The track and government take a fixed cut out of this pool, and the rest are divided up among the winners of the bet. On a normal race day, the payout is typically fairly inline with the odds. But during a big race day, the general public will throw in a lot of money on favorites as a “sure thing”. This massively inflates the pool and allows smart bettors to pocket that money.</p>



<p>See where I am going with this?</p>



<p>The Kentucky Derby is the biggest day in horse racing, which also makes it the biggest pool available. Typically more than $200,000,000 is wagered with the vast majority of that by spectators and casual bettors just wanting to turn $2 into $5 by piling on the favorite.</p>



<p>But the favorite has only won 5 out of the last 34 derbies. That’s equivalent to 8-1 odds, but the favorites are always listed as 3-1 or even 3-2. Clearly there isn’t any money to be made taking the favorite, but the public is going to do it anyway every single time.</p>



<p>That’s a good thing though, because that means the pool is bigger for the sharp bettors to cash in big.</p>



<p>This is why you can turn $10 into $20,000 during the Kentucky Derby and why I love the ponies so much!</p>



<p>I want you to get a taste of the action, especially with our friends at DRF giving you a free $10 to get started with for just signing up! (Click here to get that offer)</p>



<h3 id='my-$10-superfecta-strategy'  id="boomdevs_2" class="wp-block-heading" ><strong>My $10 Superfecta Strategy</strong></h3>



<p>In the main event, Race 12 of the Kentucky Derby, I really like the following horses:</p>



<p>#9 &#8211; Tiz the Bomb<br>#15 &#8211; White Abarrio<br>#16 &#8211; Cyber Knife<br>#6 &#8211; Messier</p>



<p>I really like #9 to win, #15 and #16 to be second or third, and #6 to be fourth. I also like horses #3, 8, and 10 as possible contenders for fourth place.</p>



<p>A $1 superfecta bet on this race is projected to pay over $20,000. So we’re going to use your free $10 to create 10 superfecta bets using these horses to increase our odds of hitting the jackpot!</p>



<p>This is what the bets look like &#8211; don’t worry, I’ll explain how to place them in a moment:</p>



<p>$1 Superfecta:<br>9 with 15, 16 with 15, 16, with 3, 6, 8, 10</p>



<p>$1 Superfecta:<br>15 with 9 with 16 with 6</p>



<p>$1 Superfecta:<br>16 with 9 with 15 with 6</p>



<p>If you were to go up to the window at Churchill Downs, you could say this to the teller and they would understand it perfectly and ask for $10 and give you your betting slips.</p>



<p>But, you can do this from the comfort of your home (legal in all states!) using DRF Bets. I’ll walk you through how to place these bets one by one.</p>



<h3 id='online-horse-betting-walkthrough'  id="boomdevs_3" class="wp-block-heading" >Online HOrse Betting <strong>Walkthrough</strong></h3>



<p>Step 1: Use this link to sign up with DRF and get your free $10.</p>



<p>Step 2: First thing Saturday morning, go to&nbsp;<a href="https://bets.drf.com/churchill-downs">https://bets.drf.com/churchill-downs</a>&nbsp;and select race 12.</p>



<p>Step 3: Where it says “Select Wager Type”, choose “SPR”. This is for Superfecta, a bet on the top 4 places.</p>



<p>Step 4: Click “$ Enter” and enter $1 as the wager amount.</p>



<p>Step 5: Select horse 9 for 1st place.</p>



<p>Step 6: Select horse 15 and 16 for 2nd place.</p>



<p>Step 7: Select horses 15 and 16 for 3rd place.</p>



<p>Step 8: Select horses 3,6,8, and 10 for 4th place.</p>



<p>Step 9: This should give you a total wager of $8, click place bet.</p>



<p>Congratulations, you’ve just placed your first exotic ticket! All this did was create a seperate superfecta bet for each possible combination of the selections we made, which is 8 total.</p>



<p>Step 10: Return to&nbsp;<a href="https://bets.drf.com/churchill-downs">https://bets.drf.com/churchill-downs</a>&nbsp;and select race 12.</p>



<p>Step 11: Where it says “Select Wager Type”, choose “SPR”.</p>



<p>Step 12: Click “$ Enter” and enter $1 as the wager amount.</p>



<p>Step 13: Select horse 15 for 1st, horse 9 for 2nd, horse 16 for 3rd, and horse 6 for fourth.</p>



<p>Step 14: Click Place bet.</p>



<p>We placed this bet in case #15 comes in first instead of #9, pushing #16 to third. If you’re keen to put some money up, go ahead and add 3,8 and 10 for fourth to increase your chances of winning.</p>



<p>Step 15: Return to&nbsp;<a href="https://bets.drf.com/churchill-downs">https://bets.drf.com/churchill-downs</a>&nbsp;and select race 12.</p>



<p>Step 16: Where it says “Select Wager Type”, choose “SPR”.</p>



<p>Step 17: Click “$ Enter” and enter $1 as the wager amount.</p>



<p>Step 18: Select horse 16&nbsp; for 1st, horse 9 for 2nd, horse 15 for 3rd, and horse 6 for fourth.</p>



<p>Step 19: Click Place bet.</p>



<p>Like the previous bet, we’re creating this one as a contingency should #16 come in first, pushing #9 to second and #15 to third. We’d typically suggest keeping 3,8,10 as fourth place options, but that would go over our budget of $10.</p>



<p>All 10 of these bets are high risk, but we’re putting the odds in our favor both through sharp handicapping as well as sharp betting strategies.</p>



<h3 id='bonus-$50-strategy'  id="boomdevs_4" class="wp-block-heading" ><strong>Bonus $50 Strategy</strong></h3>



<p>If you’re willing to put a little more money in, I would suggest this strategy for $50 budget:</p>



<p>$10 Win on 9<br>$1 Exacta Box: 9, 15, 16 ($6 total)<br>$1 Straight Trifecta: 9, 15,16 with 9,15,16, with 6,15,16 ($10)<br>$1 Straight Superfecta: 9,15,16 with 9,15,16 with 9,15,16 with 3.6,8,10, ($24)</p>



<p>The $10 winner could pay $300, the $1 exacta could pay $250, the $1 trifecta could pay $1600, and the superfecta as much as $20,000!</p>



<p>This slip pretty optimally combines the horses I feel are best to increase the odds of a winning bet paying out. If you want to bet more, I’d just increase the wager size proportionately across this strategy making your payout even bigger!&nbsp;</p>



<p>Good luck!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://winnersandwhiners.com/betting/horse-racing/kentucky-derby-superfecta-betting-strategy-to-turn-10-into-20000-454/">Kentucky Derby Superfecta Betting Strategy to turn $10 into $20,000</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://winnersandwhiners.com/betting">Winners &amp; Whiners - Sportsbooks</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
